import { Question } from '@/src/types/questions'

const hiraganaDakuten: Question[] = [
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"ga\"?",
    "options": [
      "ず",
      "ざ",
      "ど",
      "が"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "が"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"gi\"?",
    "options": [
      "べ",
      "ぢ",
      "じ",
      "ぎ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぎ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"gu\"?",
    "options": [
      "づ",
      "べ",
      "が",
      "ぐ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぐ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"ge\"?",
    "options": [
      "げ",
      "ご",
      "ぱ",
      "べ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "げ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"go\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぎ",
      "ぶ",
      "ご",
      "ぱ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ご"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"za\"?",
    "options": [
      "ざ",
      "ご",
      "ぷ",
      "ぢ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ざ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"ji\"?",
    "options": [
      "じ",
      "げ",
      "ぢ",
      "ぶ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "じ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"zu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ず",
      "ぺ",
      "ざ",
      "ど"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ず"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"ze\"?",
    "options": [
      "だ",
      "べ",
      "ぜ",
      "ぷ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぜ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"zo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぞ",
      "ぷ",
      "べ",
      "ぐ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぞ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"da\"?",
    "options": [
      "ど",
      "ぺ",
      "だ",
      "び"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "だ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"ji\"?",
    "options": [
      "で",
      "ぢ",
      "ぷ",
      "ず"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぢ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"zu\"?",
    "options": [
      "づ",
      "ぼ",
      "ぐ",
      "ぜ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "づ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"de\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぞ",
      "で",
      "ず",
      "ぜ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "で"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"do\"?",
    "options": [
      "ど",
      "で",
      "び",
      "ぷ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ど"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"ba\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぴ",
      "ご",
      "ば",
      "び"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ば"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"bi\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぷ",
      "づ",
      "び",
      "べ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "び"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"bu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぞ",
      "ぢ",
      "ぶ",
      "げ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぶ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"be\"?",
    "options": [
      "ず",
      "べ",
      "ぽ",
      "げ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "べ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"bo\"?",
    "options": [
      "づ",
      "ご",
      "ど",
      "ぼ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぼ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"pa\"?",
    "options": [
      "び",
      "ぱ",
      "ぜ",
      "で"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぱ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"pi\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぴ",
      "だ",
      "づ",
      "ぽ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぴ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"pu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぷ",
      "び",
      "ず",
      "ど"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぷ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"pe\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぶ",
      "ぽ",
      "ぺ",
      "ぼ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぺ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"po\"?",
    "options": [
      "が",
      "ぴ",
      "ぽ",
      "ぱ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぽ"
  }
]

export default hiraganaDakuten;